question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The word Inception came from the 2010 blockbuster hit Inception.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The movie The Nightmare before Christmas was all done with physical objects.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies"
                 "Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional"
                 "computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber"
                 "during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Shaquille O&#039;Neal appeared in the 1997 film &quot;Space Jam&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
